Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 6. Public Relations and Media Files, 1972-2010 TJU.2010.01.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications, 1982-2008; V.
  - Books, 1996-2008; 1.
    - Never Give In, Promotional material, 2008 (Box 1234, Folder 12)
    - Never Give In, Publishing correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 1234, Folder 13)
    - Never Give In, Publishing correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 1234, Folder 14)
    - Never Give In, Research interviews, 2006 (Box 1234, Folder 15)
    - Never Give In, Research material, 2002-2007 (Box 1234, Folder 16-17)
    - Never Give In, Working draft, 2003 (Box 1234, Folder 18)
    - Passion for Truth, Addendum, 2001 (Box 1235, Folder 1)
    - Passion for Truth, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1235, Folder 2)
    - Passion for Truth, Design and photographs, 2000 (Box 1235, Folder 3)
    - Passion for Truth, Draft, 1999 (Box 1235, Folder 4-11)
    - Passion for Truth, Draft, 1999-2000 (Box 1235, Folder 12)
    - Passion for Truth, Draft, 2000 (Box 1235, Folder 13-17)
    - Passion for Truth, Highlights and vignettes, 1999-2000 (Box 1235, Folder 18)
    - Passion for Truth, Promotional material, 2000 (Box 1236, Folder 1)
    - Passion for Truth, Publishing contract, 1997 (Box 1236, Folder 2)
    - Passion for Truth, Publishing correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 1236, Folder 3)
    - Passion for Truth, Reception, 2000-2001 (Box 1236, Folder 4)
    - Passion for Truth, Research material, 1999 (Box 1236, Folder 5)
    - Passion for Truth, Research material, 1999-2000 (Box 1236, Folder 6)
    - Passion for Truth, Research material, Clinton impeachment, 1999 (Box 1236, Folder 7-9)
    - Passion for Truth, Research material, Healthcare, 1996 (Box 1236, Folder 10-11)
    - Passion for Truth, Charles Robbins edits, 1996 (Box 1236, Folder 12)
    - Passion for Truth, Charles Robbins notes, undated (Box 1236, Folder 13)
  - Non-book, 1982-1998; 2.
    The Non-book subseries includes op-eds and letters to the editor that were authored by Senator Specter over the course of his Senate career.
    - Op-eds, 1982 (Box 1236, Folder 14)
    - Op-eds, 1992-1994 (Box 1236, Folder 15)
    - Op-eds, 1994 (Box 1236, Folder 16)
    - Op-eds, 1994-1996 (Box 1236, Folder 17)
    - Op-eds, 1995-1996 (Box 1236, Folder 18)
    - Op-eds, 1996-1998 (Box 1236, Folder 19)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1994 (Box 1236, Folder 20)
- Speeches, 1981-1999; VI.
  The Speeches series includes the text of speeches given by Senator Specter from 1981 to 1999. Senator Specter spoke on a variety of topics, including labor issues, antitrust, Israel, foreign affairs, and other. Also included here are campaign announcements, commencement speeches, and other public remarks. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - Commercial Credit Co., August 26, 1981 (Box 1237, Folder 1)
  - Rural Electric Cooperatives, August 31, 1981 (Box 1237, Folder 2)
  - Insured Savings Associations of Delaware Valley, September 25, 1981 (Box 1237, Folder 3)
  - Swiss-American Chamber of Commerce, October 1982 (Box 1237, Folder 4)
  - White House Breakfast, April 7, 1983 (Box 1237, Folder 5)
  - Commencement at Delaware Valley College, May 22, 1983 (Box 1237, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Science, April 23, 1983 (Box 1237, Folder 7)
  - American Mining Congress Coal Convention, May 16, 1983 (Box 1237, Folder 8)
  - Unknown on Israeli sovereignty, May 23, 1983 (Box 1237, Folder 9)
  - Commencement at Shippensburg University, May 5, 1984 (Box 1237, Folder 10)
  - Greater Washington Research Center, November 28, 1985 (Box 1237, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Department of AMVETS, June 20, 1987 (Box 1237, Folder 12)
  - National Urban League, July 20, 1987 (Box 1237, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, March 19, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 14)
  - Committee of Resolutions of the Republican Party Hearing, March 30, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 15)
  - Temple Israel speech on ethics, April 11, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 16)
  - Hebrew Congregation, April 12, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 17)
  - Commencement at New York University, May 26, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 18)
  - Unknown on terrorism, June 14, 1988 (Box 1237, Folder 19)
  - Northwestern University School of Law, March 17, 1989 (Box 1237, Folder 20)
  - American Friends of Haifa University, April 25, 1989 (Box 1237, Folder 21)
  - Christening of the Gettysburg, July 22, 1989 (Box 1237, Folder 22)
  - Jewish National Fund, September 26, 1989 (Box 1237, Folder 23)
  - Unknown on medical technology, May 14, 1990 (Box 1237, Folder 24)
  - Commencement at Widener University, May 19, 1990 (Box 1237, Folder 25)
  - Commencement at Army War College, June 11, 1990 (Box 1237, Folder 26)
  - Missouri Association of Republicans, February 20, 1993 (Box 1237, Folder 27)
  - Republican Party of Wisconsin, May 26, 1993 (Box 1237, Folder 28)
  - Israeli Bonds Man of the Year Dinner, December 4, 1993 (Box 1237, Folder 29)
  - Anti-Defamation League, April 19, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 30)
  - Dartmouth College, April 29, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 31)
  - Pennsylvania State University Highacres Commencement, May 13, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 32)
  - Northeast Leadership Conference, June 10, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 33)
  - Iowa GOP State Convention Fundraiser, June 24, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 34)
  - Memorial Ceremony for Senator Hugh Scott, September 19, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 35)
  - Planned Parenthood, September 29, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 36)
  - Noonan, September 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 37)
  - Anti-Defamation League, October 21, 1994 (Box 1237, Folder 38)
  - American Sephardic Federation, January 12, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 39)
  - City Club Forum, February 3, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 40)
  - Manchester, New Hampshire, February 19, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 41)
  - National Press Club, March 10, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 42)
  - Community Bankers, Harrisburg, March 10, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 43)
  - American Bar Association National Security Breakfast, March 16, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 44)
  - Presidential Campaign Announcement, March 30, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 45)
  - Issues Forum at Nixon Library, April 12, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 46)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, April 28-29, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 47)
  - Sperling Breakfast, May 3, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 48)
  - Republican National Committee, July 15, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 49)
  - Pi Lambda Phi, August 3, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 50)
  - United We Stand America, August 12, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 51)
  - Michigan Republican Mackinac Conference Breakfast, September 23, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 52)
  - Maine Straw Poll, November 4, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 53)
  - Christian Coalition, November 17, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 54)
  - Suspension of Presidential Campaign, November 22, 1995 (Box 1237, Folder 55)
  - National Association of Home Builders, January 27, 1996 (Box 1237, Folder 56)
  - Commencement at University of Pennsylvania School of Law, May 20, 1996 (Box 1237, Folder 57)
  - Teamsters, July 15, 1996 (Box 1237, Folder 58)
  - United Association of Plumbers and Pipe Fitters, August 8, 1996 (Box 1237, Folder 59)
  - Lehigh University, November 11, 1996 (Box 1237, Folder 60)
  - University of Pennsylvania Annenberg Public Policy Center, September 16, 1997 (Box 1237, Folder 61)
  - AFL-CIO National Convention, September 22, 1997 (Box 1237, Folder 62)
  - University of Pennsylvania, February 6, 1998 (Box 1237, Folder 63)
  - Remarks at Commissioning of Ensign Charles Robbins, April 21, 1999 (Box 1237, Folder 64)
  - Jefferson Medical College, May 26, 1999 (Box 1237, Folder 65)
  - AFL-CIO Speech, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 66)
  - American Muslim Council Reception, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 67)
  - Crime Speech, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 68)
  - Iowa County Prosecutors Association, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 69)
  - Lower Merion and Narberth Republican Community Lincoln Day Dinner, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 70)
  - A Winning Republican Formula, Undated (Box 1237, Folder 71)